but that's easier if you are going with the standard color like white or gray
so uh can you say that again what's the difference between those this is this is a high gloss
high gloss okay and this is a matte finish matte finish yeah high gloss is the shiny one the one
we have on the front wall i can feel that it's a little bit reflection on it yeah and matte is like
that one but it doesn't have a reflection yes so matt is a more closer to filter doors i can say
so this front wall the white and black ones are painted slab doors uh i see i see yeah i'm looking
for something that is let's say if it's damaged and then i can replace it easily i can find the
replacement is easier to find for the white one so if you are going with the trellis it's more
price friendly than painted ones okay acrylic is cheaper than paint and uh for the white ones it's
easily available i can say like i suppose you are going with the blue sometimes yeah sometimes supplier
replaced this blue shade with lighter or darker than this one yeah that is it can be a problem i see
i see i see i see i see so yeah good good call uh i will double check with that and then maybe i'll go
for the white one uh either you can do a contrast with the wooden finishes so something like this you
can do a white contrast with this one either this one what do you mean by construction it's like you
have to add a layer or top of it you know like uh base cabinets are in a white and a wall in both green
island in the border green rest all white you can do that as well so these are a little expensive than
regular acrylic ones yeah but if you like a wood grain finishes you can add these ones for some
washrooms or for a high light part of the kitchen gotcha uh how much will those cost is it like you'll be uh
like how many percentage 20 30 percent it's easier than the white one or then the white one maybe it's uh
15 to 20 percent 15 to 20 percent yeah because the the wood color will be make the house looks more
warm i would say those ones so white ones will give you a good price for the colored ones the comparison
is 10 to 15 percent maybe with the white it will be more i'm not sure with the white the only difference is
uh white ones we bought in a bulk so we got a deal price on white ones for the other colors price is a
little higher than the white gotcha gotcha i see i see okay fair enough yeah because i personally have
a firm um um i don't know to be honest i don't have any preferences i want i want something long lasting
long lasting easy to replace easy to fix and then so anytime you say hey uh the ball is broken
the thing is gone bye bye and i need to be replaced then i can hey i can come back here okay oh i need
to buy something if damage is gonna happen very regularly then painted is best like it's easy to do the
touch-ups on paint then the acrylic so on acrylic one if something is damaged we have to replace the whole
door so that thing is okay so i can say hey i got the size and this doll need to be yes you're gonna get
the new new one yes things like that okay um yeah i will think about that i think that is a good point
if i get for the white one what about those one those are wood material is it is it okay to replace
or you may not be able to find the same color same type uh most probably it will be same but we can't
predict future yeah like if something is discontinued from employer's side like sale is not that good
they switched color with something else so we're not sure about that scenario makes sense makes sense
because anyone sees how to say yeah because it's uh for buddha grind it's personal choice why it is
you give me the idea of the white one will be easy to find because yeah anywhere is like the white one
yeah yes yes that makes sense that makes sense definitely okay i have i have some idea right now
because i'm still looking for what kind of stuff i need okay if you have any pictures you can show me
uh for the for the design for the design i see i don't really have any design right now
uh the only thing i have is uh from from um give me one sec i think i may have one uh see the best
um this one um so um that is from the see the best company and he they they have a many project here
and then i believe this one maybe yeah so this one the kitchen comes out this one can i see
sure it doesn't allow me to click and full screen okay so this is a high gloss acrylic they make
islander in different color whole cabinet trays of this material just the island is something like this
yeah whole is the like high gloss white high gloss contrasted with the gray something like this maybe
they got the the lights on and make the refreshing and make the the the cabinet looks good yeah still
it's a high gloss material white high gloss acrylic gotcha gotcha yeah so you like something this one's
islands color is different and rest all cabinet trees in one color actually for the renovation that i'm
going to do i'm not going to do any cap uh iceland so i'm going to remove the iceland slow iceland
so and then i'm just going to do the kitchen or the cabinet and all the things and regarding uh
refreshing or no reflection and i talk i i didn't know because when i show my family hey which one you
like my family say hey this this looks good and okay so for cleaning purpose maintenance purpose high
gloss is easy to maintain matte is a bit hard why because on gloss if you wipe something it's gonna
clean easily for matte you can feel the texture if something is spilled on this that will go to the panel
and it needs to be cleaned very like i can say hardly gotcha gotcha yeah gloss ones are easy to maintain
got it another question is about the um the material let's say if i go for this uh this material here
yeah it got the reflection looks good and then the touch is smooth so good everything is good but the
thing is uh let's say um is it if i put the water on it like maybe i think 10 hours maybe 20 hours is it
get inside yeah get inside and then get like if it's spilled you clean no damage if water is staying on
the panel for long hours it may okay how long is like like the uh there's a time limit here because
i did some research they say some material that can last the water maybe 24 hours some can last few days
some can stand for never sure because before whenever customers ask us what's like water resistant
resistant of this material only till that like if something is spills uh we recommend them to
clean right way yeah yeah water is on the panel for long hours it might affect we are not sure as well
gotcha gotcha because uh it really um depends on the situation because there's a
acrylic comes as well that is uh water resistant and fire resistant like different than this one
but that is uh very expensive oh yes yes that's why i have those samples here as well so these are
water and fire resistant but this is uh more expensive yeah i can say two times and two three times
then yeah that's why i want to have something easy to replace that's why i want to have something
that is easy to replace so let's say if something is damaged i can yeah if something is
like that they need to replace something we need to order a panel so it's a special order
suppliers are not keeping these ones in their stocks they also have to order from them
it's gonna take longer time than thread gotcha gotcha so so uh so um so why not i got the idea so if i
want to get something maybe the best option is get the white with the uh this one and then um maybe i
i don't know maybe the white uh countertop as well so make everything white i don't know it's like
then you have options for the contour so you can go with something like this like white but have a
variations in it like different colors oh this this feeling is different this is not that yeah that is
different so this is the cheaper one it's just three quarter thick okay yeah three quarters so it's like
not that thing or it's not like uh that much heavy duty so it's ancient quarter and polished on top
this is just three quarter slab oh i see i see so is it that that is um uh stone or wood inside or
because this whole thing is solid you can i see i see okay because this one i don't know it's like i
touch on it i feel is cheap the feeling this is cheaper than that one that feels we're just keeping
it as an option but but but uh personally personally for more i say i like the thin one i don't like the
fake one exactly the big one is is too heavy too heavy i want to keep everything simple easy to maintain
and lightweight so we can go with something from this book oh i can feel it yeah we are dealing with the
lady the fabricator ladies name is youtube so we are dealing with them if you like something from this one
we can also do the order for you i see i see i see um so right now i don't have any preference so
in my opinion this and this and that looks same sorry
they all have slight variations so in this one pattern is really merged on that one the color is like
gray it's uh suspended all over so on this one variations is different kind of so all is about
the pattern color is white yeah the only thing is i feel this one is feel cheaper cheaper yes that is
like a bit rough but but they look all same tone for me
and the other one you can go with actually any option from whatever you can get like best price i can say
the other one i found i i see there's a good one here this one um this one is slightly i i i i
like this one like this one like this one it looks so cool it's got a little shiny here and this is also from
this one yeah this one looks uh little bit more like i don't know is it this is a good one or or
natural stone or what is it i think good ones like quite thicker yeah i just like that the little shiny
uh like a sprinkle something like that thank you yeah okay but i don't know is it this one is good for
maintenance or no questions can answered by the question i don't have much about this but i just
know that three quarters you put an inch and quarter okay uh so uh the finish so this is the three
quarter this is the ancient quarter the one we have right there that one that is three that has a finger
yeah i see so okay um yeah i don't know i don't know this one this one i they are all the same for
me but this one looks slightly different and it doesn't look that white and meanwhile it still keep the
keep the style here and little bit dark here this is what i like personally okay and yeah we can see
if we can find something like this on their display so that you can get the product code of this one
okay yeah this is the only thing i see
but uh yeah this one looks like like a milk something like this maybe it's the same
and also this one i see some of the cabinet they use this handler what do you recommend it should i
maybe use those or maybe use something like these are more functional than those ones so those are like
for a decorative purpose these are easy to pull things okay more reliable yes more reliable and
if we are using every day it's more easy to pull with these ones i see i see yeah yeah
because one of my concern is uh after a long time use this those um get loose same thing
these ones also have two of the best i see i see i see i see okay like for these ones if something
is heavier in draw it will be harder to pull oh so yeah because you are pulling with your uh finger
finger finger finger so yeah that one you can pull easier oh you see gotcha okay makes sense um good
and the other questions is about the uh the corner uh i think those are for the okay this is the
one thing i wonder is for those corner uh things um is it easy to replace this one let's say if it's broken i
worry about it's broken maybe after five years it's broken then can i buy a new one and then put it back and
a bit technical question maybe it's not that easy yeah because it looks tricky because there's gonna
be not extra space inside yes yes i wonder it's like hey if if five years later this thing is broken
and i'm going to buy a new one can i replace it and i need to replace the whole unit yeah i'm going
to replace the whole unit but the question is do i need to take out the whole cabinet or just take out
the fan let me ask the guy
maybe i will ask you one more questions before you ask the guy so every question is about the uh
the garbage bin can i do like a custom size i have a garbage bin that i want to put the custom
size contribution okay so or i have to use this the the one you you build in the one uh as we also bought
from marathon or ratio they have different size options 18 24 16 15 okay yes the maximum is 24 inches wide
or if you want to put your bin something out then we will make a pull out cabinet so that was when can
be put there oh pull out cabinet and then put it yes but then there will be a challenge height should be
between the like whatever space you have inside the cabinet from the bottom of this pull out rack
so you should have to go with that size gotcha gotcha like market do have that got it got it make sense
because i was thinking about the garbage bin but i just wonder should i use my own because i
if you want to use your arms just uh check the height should be should not be more than 27 inches
but the other questions is if i get the bin from the company say hey uh if i want to buy a new one
should i like to ask them another question that's the replacement so for the bins it's easy to replace
and uh maybe one win is around 300 or something yeah so if you need that we can install that for you
oh okay yeah so like if something if it's broken and then oh yeah okay yeah if it's broken if it's
neither if the bin is lost or if the the the rail is broken or the whole thing then i can buy the
replacement easily so that's my question so if you say hey the company calls and you cannot buy the bin you
have to redo your cabinet oh my god that would be no no if your garbage bin got damaged or something
happening you can let us know we will order a new one the replacement cost we will uh give you
like whatever is costing the bin and whatever will be uninstall and reinstall okay gotcha yeah
because uh that's all i want to know everything should be easy to maintain one and like after
cabinetry install if it's under one to two years like screw is loose or slides need to be adjust that
will be free of cost but if it's like damaged after four years five years then there will be extra
charges for this extra charge is fine the only thing i concern is if something some part need to be
replaced or need to be fixed and after five or six years i cannot find the company that would be the
no no it will be easier because these bins comes in a standard sizes so this is for 18 inches
almost on every online website you can find it easy okay so so it will be easy to find even the company
is nothing you said i still can find something similar yes you can find something from amazon or any other
online even you can go with the marathon that is what i want to hear yeah and everyone is like i see um yeah
i'm looking for the thing as well of course i think i don't know it's like why now the modern market the
people maybe like the bigger thing the better oh my god i can get a big thing and i see something they have
the the sauce uh uh uh accessory or a section or the path the path so what happens is like the thing they
can put the things on the thing and then do the cutting and thing so do you have that kind of thing maybe this is like
the plumbing company's question yeah because we don't carry it but our partner's friend have plumbing company
so they can recommend you to them oh elegant bath maybe you heard about it mm-hmm yeah okay so is it
that i should contact with the yes you can contact them they have a faucet sink and all stuff okay their
company name is elegant bath okay sure once you are finished here you can check with them if you have
time today yeah uh how does it spell uh e-l-e-g-a-n-t okay elegant space space bath no not a space so it's
elegant uh oh space yes space bath yes elegant bath sorry okay gotcha oh yes so they are at 132 and 78
avenue gotcha maybe i should take a look go and take a look again yes you can also because i'm also
looking for the shower stuff oh good good that's what i'm looking for thank you yeah you can give them a
name if you want to write down in your notes sure sure i i put that i already put it in also so i got the
voice memo here so okay uh how to spell sorry h-e-r h-e-r h-e-e-r h-e-r h-e-r a as apple a r j i t space t o o r
Harjitur. Harjitur. Nice to meet you. Okay, I will definitely take a look at that one. Yeah, I think that is most of my cabinet. Oh, yes. Another question I would ask is about the life. Is it that it needs to be installed with the cabinet or we need to coordinate with the electrician?
So you need to let us know before we make the cabinetry where you guys leave the wires and all stuff. So if it's a puck light, we will make the holes on the job site and leave it. The electrician will install there. So if it's an LED light, you need to drop off that strip sample channel. So we will make the grooves from here and send this stuff to the job site.
Yeah, because I want to do the LED one. But one of my concerns is, again, is it easy to replace the LED? I know how to do the LED things. So I know how to connect. But I don't know if it's right.
So on the cabinetry purpose, we will make the grooves. So it's easy like every time.
Every time, yes.
Yeah, just tape. Because I wonder, hey, if I tape it and then later on it's broken, just peel it off and then we tape the new one and then, is it that okay?
I'm not sure about that part. The only thing I know that we make the grooves here.
Gotcha, gotcha. Maybe I will double-check with Nick.
Electrician.
Yeah, the electrician and Nick can see their opinion. Because I do see those ones, but I never replace those ones, so I don't know how easy.
I do my home stuff, so I know how to replace those ones. But for the cabinet ones, I don't touch. So I don't know.
Okay.
So that would be another question. So you know what I mean? It's like I want everything to be easy to replace, easy to maintain.
Yes.
It's maintainable. I don't want to think, hey, I installed that one a few years later. It's broken. I cannot replace it. Damn, it's like wasted.
Yeah, I can ask if that's easy to replace. I'm not sure about that corner unit. But for these lights and all stuff, we will make 3D renderings for you, the layout.
Over there, we will mark wherever you need lights, where is glass cabinetry, where is solid doors, whatever you like, we will decide on that.
Gotcha. Good, good, good. Yeah, that's what I want to see and hear. And I think that is all my questions.
Yeah. Good.
Can I ask you this part around him? Is it easy to replace or not?
I won't expect it to be too easy, but I will expect to say, hey, you think that is replaceable. So do I need to tear down the whole cabinet to replace or just take it out and then replace it?
Yeah. So I don't need to take down the cabinet. Just unscrew it with that and then pick it out and then put the new one inside and install it? Okay, good. That's what I saw already. Okay.
Same school, same bed, everything same. Gotcha. Nice. Yeah, that's what I want. And last time, last time I talked with, I think one of cabinet guys, they say there's another one, they call it new one, it's for the corners. I can pull the things out. I don't know if it's bad.
Pull out drawers? I don't know. I can show you one thing. Is there any other corner stuff? I can see the corner stuff you're talking about, the one we can pull out?
I don't know. That is called magic corner. Okay. We don't have in our showroom, but I can show you the picture of that one on my phone.
Sure. Maybe something on YouTube? Magic corner? Yeah, magic corner. Okay. It will be easy to see if I got a video. Magic corner.
check on this one yes